insidemylaptop.com 2019-02-04

# Privacy Policy – Inside my laptop

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  
Some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
InsideMyLaptop.com uses cookies to verify who you are. This is purely a convenience, so that the visitor won’t need to re-type all their information (name, email address, website address) again when they want to leave another comment.

### DoubleClick DART cookies

InsideMyLaptop.com also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### Web Beacons

Web beacons, also called web bugs and clear GIFs are used in combination with cookies to help people running websites to understand the behavior of their customers. A web beacon is typically a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a site or in an email. The use of a web beacon allows the site to record the simple actions of the user opening the page that contains the beacon.

InsideMyLaptop.com itself doesn’t collect or use web beacons. Some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) use web beacons on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these web beacons.

### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies, web beacons and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Chitika, Commision Junction etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links

This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. You acknowledge that InsideMyLaptop.com is not responsible for the operation of or content located on or through any such site. Links provided on this Web site are for your convenience only. Access them at your own risk. Linked sites are neither under the control of nor endorsed by InsideMyLaptop.com
